iimahd.ernet.in 2019-12-31

# 

## PRIVACY POLICY

Last Revised: 12/18/2019

 ** _To view our archived Privacy Policy, click_**[ ** _here_**](https://www.godaddy.com/legal/agreements/archived-privacy-policy) ** _._**

GoDaddy Media Temple, Inc. cares about your privacy. For this reason, we collect and use personal information only as needed to deliver our products, services, websites and mobile applications, and to communicate with you about the same, or as you have requested (collectively, our “Services”). Your personal information includes information such as:

  * Name
  * Address
  * Telephone number
  * Email address
  * Billing and payment information
  * Candidate information (for job applicants)
  * Other data collected that could directly or indirectly identify you.

Our Privacy Policy not only explains how and why we use your personal information that we collect, but also how you can access, update or otherwise take control of your personal information.

If at any time you have questions about our practices or any of your rights described below, you may reach our Data Protection Officer (“DPO”) and our dedicated team that supports this office by contacting us at privacy@mediatemple.net. This inbox is actively monitored and managed so that we can deliver an experience that you can confidently trust.

### What information we collect, how we collect it, and why

Much of what you likely consider personal information is collected directly from you when you:

  1. create an account or purchase any of our Services (ex: billing information, including name, address, credit card number, government identification);
  2. request assistance from our award-winning customer support team (ex: phone number);
  3. complete contact forms or request newsletters or other information from us (ex: email); or
  4. participate in contests and surveys, apply for a job, or otherwise participate in activities we promote that might require information about you.

However, we also collect additional information when delivering our Services to you to ensure necessary and optimal performance. These methods of collection may not be as obvious to you, so we thought we’d highlight and explain a bit more about what these might be (as they vary from time to time):

 **Cookies and similar technologies** on our websites and our mobile applications allow us to track your browsing behavior, links clicked, items purchased, your device type, and to collect various data, including analytics, about how you use and interact with our Services. These technologies automatically collect data when you use and interact with our Services, including metadata, log files, cookie/device IDs, page load time, server response time, and approximate location information to measure website performance and improve our systems, including optimizing DNS resolution, network routing and server configurations. Specifically, interactions with the features, content and links (including those of third-parties, such as social media plugins) contained within the Services, Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type and settings, the date and time the Services were used, information about browser configuration and plugins, language preferences and cookie data, information about devices accessing the Services, including type of device, what operating system is used, device settings, application IDs, unique device identifiers and error data is collected. All this allows us to provide you with more relevant product offerings, a better experience on our sites and mobile applications, and to collect, analyze and improve the performance of our Services. We may also collect your location (IP address) so that we can personalize our Services. For additional information, and to learn how to manage the technologies we utilize, please visit our Cookie Policy. If you wish to opt out of interest-based advertising click [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/) [or if located in the European Union click [here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)]. Please note you will continue to receive generic ads. 

**Supplemented Data** may be received about you from other sources, including publicly available databases or third parties from whom we have purchased data, in which case we may combine this data with information we already have about you so that we can update, expand and analyze the accuracy of our records, assess the qualifications of a candidate for employment, identify new customers, and provide products and services that may be of interest to you. If you provide us personal information about others, or if others give us your information, we will only use that information for the specific reason for which it was provided to us.

 **How we utilize information.**

We strongly believe in both minimizing the data we collect and limiting its use and purpose to only that (1) for which we have been given permission, (2) as necessary to deliver the Services you purchase or interact with, or (3) as we might be required or permitted for legal compliance or other lawful purposes:

 **Delivering, improving, updating and enhancing our Services.** We collect various information relating to your purchase, use and/or interactions with our Services. We utilize this information to:

  * Improve and optimize the operation and performance of our Services (again, including our websites and mobile applications)
  * Diagnose problems with and identify any security risks, errors, or needed enhancements to the Services
  * Detect and prevent fraud and abuse of our Services and systems
  * Collecting aggregate statistics about use of the Services
  * Understand and analyze how you use our Services and what products and services are most relevant to you.

Much of the data collected is aggregated or statistical data about how individuals use our Services, and is not linked to any personal information.

 **Sharing with trusted third parties.** We may share your personal information with affiliated companies within our corporate family, with third parties with which we have partnered to allow you to integrate their services into our own Services, and with trusted third party service providers as necessary for them to perform services on our behalf, such as:

  * Processing credit card payments
  * Serving advertisements
  * Conducting contests or surveys
  * Performing analysis of our Services and customers demographics
  * Communicating with you, such as by way of email or survey delivery
  * Customer relationship management
  * Recruiting support and related services.

We only share your personal information as necessary for any third party to provide the services as requested or as needed on our behalf. These third parties (and any subcontractors they may be permitted to use) are subject to strict data processing terms and conditions and are prohibited from utilizing, sharing or retaining your personal information for any purpose other than as they have been specifically contracted for (or without your consent).

We may also share your information with third parties for the purpose of facilitating / allowing a merger, acquisition or sale of all or substantially all of our assets, in which case the acquiring company may continue to utilize your data in the manner for which it was provided and intended.

 **Communicating with you.** We may contact you directly or through a third party service provider regarding products or services you have signed up or purchased from us, such as necessary to deliver transactional or service related communications. We may also contact you with offers for additional services we think you’ll find valuable if you give us consent, or where allowed based upon legitimate interests. You don’t need to provide consent as a condition to purchase our goods or services. These contacts may include:

  * Email
  * Telephone calls

You may also update your subscription preferences with respect to receiving communications from us and/or our partners by signing into your account and visiting “Account Settings” page.

If we collect information from you in connection with a co-branded offer, it will be clear at the point of collection who is collecting the information and whose privacy policy applies. In addition, it will describe any choice options you have in regards to the use and/or sharing of your personal information with a co-branded partner, as well as how to exercise those options. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of third-party sites. Please read the privacy policy of any website you visit.

If you believe that anyone has provided us with your personal information and you would like to request that it be removed from our database, please contact us at privacy@mediatemple.net. 

**Transfer of personal information abroad.** If you utilize our Services from a country other than the country where our servers are located, your personal information may be transferred across international borders. Also, when you call us or initiate a chat, we may provide you with support from one of our global locations outside your country of origin.

 **Compliance with legal, regulatory and law enforcement requests.** We cooperate with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (such as subpoena requests), to protect our property and rights or the property and rights of a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity we consider to be illegal or unethical.

To the extent we are legally permitted to do so, we will take reasonable steps to notify you in the event that we are required to provide your personal information to third parties as part of legal process. We will also share your information to the extent necessary to comply with any ICANN, registry or ccTLD rules, regulations and policies when you register a domain name with us. For reasons critical to maintaining the security, stability and resiliency of the Internet, this includes the transfer of domain name registration information to the underlying domain registry operator and escrow provider, and publication of that information as required by ICANN in the public WHOIS database or with other third parties that demonstrate a legitimate legal interest to such information.

### How we secure, store and retain your data.

We follow generally accepted standards to store and protect the personal information we collect, both during transmission and once received and stored, including utilization of encryption where appropriate.

We retain personal information only for as long as necessary to provide the Services you have requested and thereafter for a variety of legitimate legal or business purposes. These might include retention periods:

  * mandated by law, contract or similar obligations applicable to our business operations;
  * for preserving, resolving, defending or enforcing our legal/contractual rights; or
  * needed to maintain adequate and accurate business and financial records.

If you have any questions about the security or retention of your personal information, you can contact us at privacy@mediatemple.net.

### How you can access, update or delete your data.

To easily access, view or update your subscription preferences, please sign into your Account and visit your account settings. If you wish to delete or port your personal information, you may submit your request to privacy@mediatemple.net. If you make a request to delete your personal information and that data is necessary for the products or services you have purchased, the request will be honored only to the extent it is no longer necessary for any Services purchased or required for our legitimate business purposes or legal or contractual record keeping requirements.

If you are unable for any reason to access your Account Settings, you may also contact us by one of the methods described in the “Contact Us” section below.

### The E.U-U.S and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Frameworks.

Our parent company, GoDaddy Operating Company, LLC (and our related entities, including GoDaddy.com, LLC, Blue Razor Domains, LLC, Starfield Technologies, LLC, Domains by Proxy, LLC, Outright, Inc., Mad Mimi, Inc. and Media Temple, Inc.) participates in and has certified its compliance with the EU-U.S. and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework. GoDaddy Operating Company, LLC is committed to subjecting all personal information received from the EU or Switzerland, in reliance on the Privacy Shield Framework, to the Framework’s applicable Principles. To learn more about the Privacy Shield Framework, visit the U.S. Department of Commerce’s [Privacy Shield List](https://www.privacyshield.gov/list).

GoDaddy Media Temple, Inc. is responsible for the processing of personal information it receives, under each Privacy Shield Framework, and subsequently transfers to a third party acting as an agent on its behalf. GoDaddy Media Temple, Inc. complies with the Privacy Shield Principles for all onward transfers of personal information from the EU and Switzerland, including the onward transfer liability provisions.

With respect to personal information received or transferred pursuant to each Privacy Shield Framework, GoDaddy Media Temple, Inc. is subject to the regulatory enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission. In certain situations, GoDaddy Media Temple, Inc. may be required to disclose personal information in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>. Under certain conditions, more fully described on the [Privacy Shield website](https://www.privacyshield.gov/), you may invoke binding arbitration when other dispute resolution procedures have been exhausted.

In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, GoDaddy Media Temple, Inc. commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal information. EU and Swiss individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy Shield policy should first contact us in any manner provided in the "CONTACT US" section below in this Privacy Policy.

GoDaddy Media Temple, Inc. has further committed to cooperate with the panel established by the EU data protection authorities (DPAs) and the Swiss Federal Data Protection and Information Commissioner (FDPIC) with regard to unresolved Privacy Shield complaints concerning human resources data transferred from the EU and Switzerland in the context of the employment relationship.

###  _‘Do Not Track’_ notifications.

Some browsers allow you to automatically notify websites you visit not to track you using a “Do Not Track” signal. There is no consensus among industry participants as to what “Do Not Track” means in this context. Like many websites and online services, we currently do not alter our practices when we receive a “Do Not Track” signal from a visitor’s browser. To find out more about “Do Not Track,” you may wish to visit [www.allaboutdnt.com](https://allaboutdnt.com/).

### Age restrictions.

Our Services are available for purchase only for those over the age of 18. Our Services are not targeted to, intended to be consumed by or designed to entice individuals under the age of 18. If you know of or have reason to believe anyone under the age of 18 has provided us with any personal information, please contact us.

### Non-Discrimination.

We will not discriminate against you for exercising any of your privacy rights. Unless permitted under applicable laws, we will not:

  * Deny you goods or services.
  * Charge you different prices or rates for goods or services, including through granting discounts or other benefits, or imposing penalties.
  * Provide you a different level or quality of goods or services.
  * Suggest that you may receive a different price or rate for goods or services or a different level or quality of goods or services.

### Changes to this policy.

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to this Privacy Policy and any other places we deem appropriate, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page, at least thirty (30) days prior to the implementation of the changes.

### Data Protection Authority.

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA) and believe we maintain your personal information subject to the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), you may direct questions or complaints to your local supervisory authority or our lead supervisory authority, the UK's Information Commissioner’s Office, as noted below:

Information Commissioner’s Office

Wycliffe House, Water Lane, Wilmslow, Cheshire, SK9 5AF, United Kingdom

Phone: 0303 123 1113

### Contact us.

If you have any privacy-related questions, concerns or complaints about our Privacy Policy, our practices or our Services, you may contact our Office of the DPO by email at privacy@godaddy.com. In the alternative, you may contact us by either of the following means:

  * By Mail: Attn: Office of the Data Protection Officer, 14455 North Hayden Road, Suite 219, Scottsdale, AZ 85260 USA, or for customers established in the EEA, Attn: Legal, Office of the DPO, 5th Floor, The Shipping Building, Old Vinyl Factory, 252-254 Blyth Road, Hayes, UB3 1HA.
  * By Phone: 877.578.4000

 ** _We will respond to all requests, inquiries or concerns within thirty (30) days._**
